Guide to the Truman A. Warner Papers MS 026
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series I, Research Files
  - Sources-Genealogy
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Notitia Parochialis of Rev. Thomas Davies A.M., 1763-1766 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Baptisms (p.51-62).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) The Foster Bible. Jonah Foster, Pub. 1824, 1769-1933 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Births/deaths/marriages of Foster and allied families (p.63-65). (1935, now in possession of Arthur Foster)
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Genealogy of Samuel Camp and Sarah Dibble, 1793-1931, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriage/births/deaths of Camp and allied families (p.66-69). (Loaned by Sarah Camp Hawley)
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Genealogy of Amos Lake and his first wife Catherine Blackman, and second wife Mary Ann Bennett, 1785-1931, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Lake and allied families (p.70-74).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy), undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Record of (blank) owned by Sarah Camp Hawley, 1734-1784. Samuel Camp came from Old Milford, settled and buried in Newtown. Names of children and allied families (p.75-78).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Bible of Mrs. Mary Edgett, 1781-1934 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Edgett and allied families (p.79-83). Published Boston 1832
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Bible of Samuel N. McKay, Bible of Albert? Mckay, 1775-1921, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of McKay and allied families (p.84-86). Printed Philadelphia 1858
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Bible of Mrs. Joseph Francher, formerly Robert Powell White's, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of White and allied families (p.87-92) Published 1857
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Samuel Hurd Bible, 1771-1879 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Hurd and allied families (p.93-95). (Bible owned by Mrs. Albert Pulling)
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Bible of Benjamin Ambler, 1787-1911, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Ambler and allied families (p.96-98). (Owned by Mrs. Joseph E. Hoagson)
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Little Bible, 1727-1851, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Ambler/Hurd families (p.99) Printed 1846
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Paper from Miss Bacon's Bible, 1653-1907, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Bacon and allied families (p.100-104).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Hoyt Bible (Mrs. H. H. Barroll) 1786-1924, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Hoyt and allied families (p.105-108). Marriages/births/deaths of Hoyt and allied families (p.105-108). Published 1839.
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Ives Bible, 1796-1928 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Ives and allied families (p.109-112). (Bible loaned by Miss Parmelee).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Bible of Ed Wheeler, 1806-1871 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriage and births of Amgi Wheeler (p.113).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) The Waterbury Family Bible, 1763-1918 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Waterbury family (p.114-121). (Original owner Deodate Waterbury)
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Frost Bible, 1795-1920, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Frost and allied families (p.122-123). (Offered by Mrs. George Hawley)
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) John Tweedy and Descendants written by Edgar S. Tweedy, 1744-1931 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Tweedy and allied families (p.124-135).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) S.A.R. Record of Ernest Leroy Hatch from Family Bible, 1753-1933 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Hatch and allied families (p.136)
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) E. H. Pearce's Records, p.4, 1624-1761, undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births of Sherwood/Taylor families (p.137).
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Family Bible of Hoyt Dibble, 1812-1899 (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Marriages/births/deaths of Dibble and allied families (p.138-139). (Given to D.A.R. by Mrs. V. Sherman of Danbury) Published by H. & E. Phinney Cooperstown, NY, 1838.
    - Julia Brush Records (copy) Received from Bristol, Conn., undated (Box 26, Folder 74-77)
      Records of numerous families from Bristol. (last page of booklet)
    - New Milford Church Records (original), 1716-1802 (Box 26, Folder 78)
      Baptisms, deaths, and church members.
    - New Milford Church Records (copy), 1716-1802 (Box 26, Folder 79)
      Deaths (p.1-9) Congregational Church Baptisms, 1748-1758 (p.10-13) Admitted to church at New Milford, 1716-1782 (p.14-17) An account of ye Breatheren of ye Church at ye first Settlement of ye Minister in New Milford. Some records imperfect for ye want of a Book. (p.18-27).
    - Church of Christ Records - Danbury (copy), 1770-1797 (Box 26, Folder 80)
      Marriages, October 10, 1770-1779 Baptisms, September 23, 1770-1779 Deaths, 1772-1797 Connecticut State Library - Research Items, 1636-1944 (w/gaps) See: Sources-Danbury and Connecticut History (Box 25, folder 53) Connecticut State Library Research, 1976-1977 See: Sources-Danbury and Connecticut History (Box 26, folders 11-12)
    - Dean, "Religious Sentiments" [1890], undated (Box 26, Folder 81)
      Original note to Dealia Stebbins, Ridgefield, signed "Miss Dean." Includes handwritten transcript by Truman Warner.
    - Hawley, George M., Ledger, 1901-1902 (Box 26, Folder 82)
      Copy of ledger. Original in possession of Mrs. Stephen Evanuska.
    - Hoyt, Benjamin, Diary (copy), 1778-1844 (Box 26, Folder 83)
      Research notes and retrospective sketch of his life.
    - Johnson, Ruth - Smith-Hoyt Genealogy, undated (Box 26, Folder 84-85)
      Photographs (20 b/w images) of old places on Ely Street, South Norwalk, CT., identified by family names. Reminiscences of Ely Neck Road by Wilbur F. Smith, grandson of Daniel Hoyt 3rd. Extracts from Halls History of Norwalk, 1843. Hand drawn map of old Ely Neck Road 1840. map of old Ely Neck Road 1840.
    - Journal of Joseph Joslin Jr. (copy), 1777-1778 (Box 26, Folder 86)
      Journal of Joseph Joslin Jr. of South Killingly. A Teamster in the Continental Service. March 1777-August 1778. (p.299-369). See also: American Revolution.
    - Kellogg Diaries - 19th Century, 1962-1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Clippings from The Brookfield Journal. Excerpts from the Diary of Barzillai Buckley Kellogg that describes life in agricultural Brookfield. The newspaper also published a journal kept by Barzillai while on his honeymoon six years later in 1845. Both journals were printed through the courtesy of Mrs. Charles Ryder, granddaughter of Barzillai Buckley Kellogg.
    - Langdon, Timothy, Papers (copy), 1781-1785 (Box 26, Folder 87)
      A Creed prepared by Rev. Timothy Langdon of Danbury explaining his belief in God dated April 27, 1783, last will and testament, and letters addressed to Mr. Baldwin.
    - Lepper, H. George, Accounts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 88)
      Danbury News Times article, research notes, and two essays written by H. George Lepper entitled Druggist & Apothecary dated August 1974 and The Way It Was dated April 1975. George Lepper, a pharmacist in Danbury, recalls the days in 1915 when he became an apprentice to a druggist at Stevens' Drug Store, and his subsequent career as a pharmacist.
    - Lockwood, Edward-Civil War Letters (copies), 1862-1865 (Box 26, Folder 89-90)
      Original letter to Mr. & Mrs. Herman Keeler of Lysander, NY, signed by Eddy (Edward P.) Lockwood, June 24, 1863. Copies of additional letters to friends from Lockwood, Frank S. Chapman, and Dewitt Perin? during the Civil War. Handwritten note: "Civil War Letters from Abner Keeler, April 1950. Owned by Frank Stone in 1977." See also: American Civil War.
    - Wills and Inventory Records, 1675-1798, undated (Box 27, Folder 5-7)
      Thomas Barnum 1730-1731; Samuel Benedict 1718; Samuel Benedict 1735; Zadock Benedict 1798; John Bouton 1704-05; Francis Bushnell 1697; Thomas Dean 1730; Ezra Dibble 1739; John Hoyt 1712; Joshua Hoyt 1726-1727; and Ebenzer Knapp. Inventories: Thomas Barnum Estate n.d.; Thomas Barnum Sr. 1696; Francis Bushnell 1697; Daniell Gun 1723-1724; and Joseph Forward 1704.
    - McCarthy, Sara H., Diary (copy), 1914-1918 (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
      Sara was the wife of John McCarthy of McCarthy Coal Company, Danbury, Connecticut. Sara belonged to a prominent and influential family whose lives revolved around their children, friends, relatives, church, and social activities in the early 1900s.
    - McNally, Thomas, Papers (copy), 1929 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Councilman, Fourth Ward. Letters giving McNally an opportunity to accept the position of General Organizer for the United Hatters for a temporary period of six months in South Norwalk and vicinity. Speech directed to a radio audience on the question of employment and safety practices in foundries. See also: Truman Warner Papers: Book.
    - Merrill, Albert, Journal, 1633-1896 (copy), undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Written by Clarence Merrill, Salt Lake, Utah. Traces the Merrill family history from approximately 1633 to 1896.
    - Orgelman, Hamilton, Notes, 1898-1908 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Recollection of his boyhood in Danbury, Conn. dated December 24, 1973
    - Osborne, Lucy Maria (copies), 1907 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Research notes and biographical sketch of Miss Lucy Maria Osborne from The Danbury Evening News, Dec. 3, 1907, on the occasion of her 100th birthday.
    - Purdy, Horace, 1860-1867 (Box 28, Folder 9-13)
      Research notes from Horace Purdy's diary and typescript of original Civil War letters (dated 1861). The majority of the correspondence is to and from his wife Gussie. Other correspondents include his father Rev. E. E. Griswold, his mother Nancy Griswold, his sisters Emily Anderson and Fanny, and his brother George. Purdy was in the 1st Regiment of Connecticut Volunteers. Includes births/deaths/marriages of Rockwell family (1813-1921). See also: Truman Warner Papers: American Civil War, and Horace Purdy Diary (microfilm located in the Haas Library, Archives & Special Collections).
    - Rockwell, George L., 1937 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Early Days in Danbury by George L. Rockwell. Edited typescript of address given to teachers of Danbury Normal School, December 9, 1937, which contains a historical sketch of Danbury and prominent families during 17th and 18th centuries.
    - Rockwell Memoirs. (Alphonso David Rockwell) (copy), 1920 (Box 28, Folder 15-16)
      Rambling Recollections, An Autobiography by A. D. Rockwell, M. D. Born in New Canaan, Conn., on May 18, 1840, and migrated to Danbury when he was 5 years old.
    - Rogers, Rev. Medad, 1777-1911 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      Handwritten research notes
    - Rumrill Letters/Melville (John H. Rumrill 1824-1901), 1846-1997 (Box 28, Folder 18-22)
      Excerpts from The Individual and His Society: The Psychodynamics of Primitive Social Organizations by Abram Kardiner; letters and transcripts between James H. Rumrill and his mother, Mary Livermore, and sister Rachel Rumrill Nason of Boston between October 21, 1846, and July 28, 1901. Rumrill's journey to the South Pacific begins at the time when Herman Melville returned from his four years in the South Pacific.
    - Sears Family, n.d. (copy), undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
      History of the James Sears family who lived on Joe's Hill by Lydia V. H. Potter, p. 4-7. See also: Genealogy.
    - Shaw, Jacob, Diary (copy), 1834-1982 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      Transcript of the diary includes letters written to and from J. Shaw to the Brother John (J. Boyer), John Boyan, Peter Schoemaker, Mrs. E. Shaw, Wm. T. Scofield, Rev. H. Wing, Rev. Wm. M. A. Ferguson. Rev. Shaw was an itinerant Methodist preacher who traveled about in N.Y., Conn., and Mass. preaching the gospel. He was the minister of the Methodist Church at Redding Center from 1848-1849 and again in 1859. Stebbins, Dealia [1890] See Dean, Miss, above.
    - Taylor, Ernest L., 1971-1977 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      Oral history interview/notes, research notes, and genealogy.
    - Wanzer Diary, 1859-1861 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Describes the daily life of a farmer with particular emphasis on weather patterns. Typescript of original. Typescript of original., undated (Box 28)
    - Warren, Robert Penn and Eleanor Clark Warren, 1969-1997 (Box 28, Folder 27)
      Copies of newspaper articles and obituaries. See also: Genealogy.
  - Sources-Maps
    - Brookfield 1867, Bethel (Central Area) 1957, and U. S. Department of Interior, undated (Box OS 2, Folder *)
      Geological Survey of Danbury/Brookfield. n.d.
    - Connecticut, New England, New York, 1642-1983, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Research notes and miscellaneous articles on collecting old maps and sources.
    - Connecticut, New England, New York, 1705-1981 (Box 27, Folder 9-11)
      Danbury street maps and general highway maps.
    - Dept. of Interior, U. S. Geological Survey, Danbury, Conn. (original)., 1929 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    - Department of Interior, U. S. Geological Survey, Mass.-R.I.-Conn., 1978 (Folder OS Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Department of Interior, U. S. Geological Survey, undated (Folder OS Folder 1, Item 2-4)
      Danbury Quadrangle, 1984 (original) 2 copies (original) 2 copies 1893 Fairfield County; Bethel Quadrangle; Danbury Quadrangle; and Croton Regional Basin, n.d.
    - Geological Surveys, 1801-1993 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      Early Connecticut, Danbury Still River system, waterways of New York, Bethel, birds eye views, list of participants at the Urban Landscape Symposium sponsored by The Connecticut Historical Society, September 26, 1987.
    - Location and River, n.d., undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Copies of maps showing Danbury and the Still River with details of owners and their businesses, and railroad lines in western Connecticut.
    - Newtown, Bethel, New Fairfield Highway Maps, undated (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    - Places of the World by A. K. Lobeck, 1955 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
      Map: Redding/Weston, Easton/Saugatuck/Sasqua/Fairfield/Black Rock, 1932
    - Topographic, 1929-1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      Maps and information on the geological history of southern New England.
    - Topographical, n.d., undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
      Topographical maps and geological surveys from Norwalk to Danbury.
    - Map of Putnam County, NY, 1962 (Folder OS Folder 4)
      Appendix to Michael Flanagan's paper on The Town of Carmel and the Ruppert Brewery; Box 42, folder 1
  - Still River Watershed, Lakes, Streams, Wetlands, Swamps
    also: Record Group 8, Student Papers, Box 1, folder 27, A History of Lake Candlewood by Lynn Fernandez.
    Hydrology - Connecticut; Kaatz Ice House (Conn.); Candlewood, Lake (Conn.); Housatonic River Watershed (Conn.) -- Regional planning; Land use -- Environmental aspects -- Connecticut -- Danbury; Kenosia, Lake (Conn.); Kohanza Reservoir Dam (Conn.); Lakes -- Connecticut; Danbury (Conn.) -- Flood, 1955.; Land use -- Connecticut -- Danbury; Lillinoah, Lake (Conn.); Geology -- Connecticut -- Danbury; Groundwater -- Connecticut -- Quality; Outdoor recreation - Housatonic River Watershed (Conn.); Danbury (Conn.) -- Geography; Connecticut River Watershed; Flood control - Connecticut - Danbury; Drinking water -- Standards -- Connecticut; Water quality - Connecticut; Water-supply - Connecticut; Wetland conservation - Connecticut; Water quality - Standards - Connecticut; Zoar, Lake (Conn.); Wetlands - Connecticut; Real estate development - Connecticut - Danbury; Ponds - Connecticut; Shepaug River (Conn.); Candlewood, Lake (Conn.); Still River (Conn.) -- Conservation; Watersheds - Connecticut; Waramaug, Lake (Conn.)
    - Ball Pond, 1849-1996 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      Research notes and clippings regarding Ball Pond Estates subdivisions, pollution, and eutrophication.
    - The Connecticut River, 1941-1994 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      History of the clean up of the Connecticut River from early industrial use and pollution.
    - Dams, 1953-1995 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      Articles on Shepaug Dam, Army Corps of Engineers, DEP policies, and owners' responsibilities for the repair of again dams.
    - Housatonic Valley, 1950-1996 (Box 27, Folder 19-26)
      Articles focus on industrial pollution and the Housatonic River Study under the Wild and Scenic River Act of the 50-mile stretch from the Massachusetts border to the confluence with the Shepaug River. Current problems concern land and recreation uses of the Housatonic particularly landowners' riparian and water control rights/easements. New problems under the Federal re-licensing of Northeast Utilities' hydroelectric plants. Groundwater Protection for the Housatonic Valley Region by John Hayes, Consultant for H.V.C.E.O. (Housatonic Valley Council of Elected Officials) October 1978.
    - Map: Major Aquifers, John Hayes, Consultant, Housatonic Valley Council of, undated (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 1)
      Elected Officials, October 1978.
    - Ice Ponds/Refrigeration, 1907-1995 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      Research notes on ice harvesting, Kaatz Ice House, ice retailer Glen Spargo, New Preston Ice, and annual harvesting.
    - Kohanza Reservoir Dam, 1952-1995 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      Articles and photos of 1869 Kohanza Dam tragedy.
    - Lake Candlewood Power, 1917-1977 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      Research notes on land acquisition for the construction of Lake Candlewood, and Schagiotoke Indians federal litigation.
    - Map: CL&P, Rocky River Hydro-Electric Development Index Map, undated (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 2)
      1926-1929.
    - Map: CL&P, Rocky River Basin, Conn., Rocky River Reservoir, General, undated (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 3)
      Property Map, nd
    - Map: Lake Candlewood, Connecticut, 1960 (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 4)
      Still River Watershed, Lakes, Streams, Wetlands, Swamps (continued)
    - Lake Candlewood, 1919-1993 (Box 27, Folder 30-36)
      Political and economic impacts on Fairfield County, growth/development of local towns, and pollution problems. How the Construction of Lake Candlewood Affected the Economic and Population Re-growth of New Fairfield (no author).nd. Student research paper: A Retrospect of the Political and Economic Evolution of Candlewood Lake by Elizabeth Humphrey. 1984.
    - Lake Candlewood, 1970-1996 (Box 27, Folder 37-38)
      Pollution problems, Lattins Cove, Crystal Bay, over development, and Endothal treatment of weeds.
    - Lake Kenosia, 1850-1996 (Box 27, Folder 39)
      Personal notes and clippings describe history, social activities from 1860s to 1996
    - Lake Lillinoah and Lake Zoar, 1952-1995 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      Clippings on history and creation of Lake Zoar and Lake Lillinoah by the impoundment of the Housatonic and Shepaug Rivers.
    - Lake Waramaug, 1861-1990 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      Articles on this natural lake that is used for recreation. Land use issues concerning water, riparian rights, and conservation.
    - Old Mill Pond, 1969-1994 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      History of Old Mill Pond and Sellick Woods.
    - Rivers/Streams, 1954-1995 (Box 27, Folder 43-44)
      Clean Water Bill 1967, Water Standards Hearings at Danbury State College, Still River, Pootatuck, and East Swamp. Eutrophication, algae, and aeration. Firm Ground, Fairfield County Soil and Water Conservation District, "Sasco Brook: A Watershed Project to Reduce sources of Nonpoint Source Pollution in Coastal Areas." Summer 1994.
    - Shepaug River, 1972-1996 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      Articles focus on the future of the Shepaug River corridor, environmental, industrial, and reservoirs to provide future potable water for lower Fairfield County and Western Connecticut.
    - Still River - Geological History, 1920-1971 (Box 27, Folder 46-47)
      Research notes and geological surveys on the drainage and glacial history of the Still River Valley. State Geological and Natural History Survey, Bulletin No. 30, by Ruth Sawyer Harvey, 1920; and, The drainage and glacial history of the Still River Valley, southwestern Connecticut by Woodrow Thompson, 1971.
    - Still River, 1955-1996 (Box 27, Folder 48-50)
      Articles on the Still River meander and urbanization of the river. Still River Watershed, Lakes, Streams, Wetlands, Swamps (continued)
    - New Map of Danbury City and Township, also Bethel Borough and Township, undated (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 5)
      by The Price and Lee Company. nd
    - Still River, 1731-1996 (Box 27, Folder 51-52)
      Research notes, maps, and "A River Runs Through It, The Urbanization of Danbury's Still River."
    - Commemorative of "A River Runs Through It" Exhibit, September 30, 1996 (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Indexed Street Maps of the Greater Danbury Area, 1970 (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Still River/Danbury Floods - History, 1777- 1995 (Box 27, Folder 53)
      Research notes on the history of the 1955 floods. See also: Floods.
    - Still River Drainage/Streams/Lakes, 1851-1995 (Box 27, Folder 54-55)
      Research notes on the history into streams, local ponds, and lakes.
    - Swamps/Marshes, 1796-1994 (Box 27, Folder 56)
      Research notes on the evolution and purpose of swamps and bogs. Old Quarry Nature Center, study of groundwater, bogs, flora and fauna, and the Still River flood plain.
    - Wetlands, 1968-1995 (Box 27, Folder 57-59)
      Wetlands preservation, inland wetlands legislation, revised Fairfield County Wetlands Maps, soil conservation, Wiels Dam, Snug Harbor sub-division, Danbury east swamp, and fairgrounds. Connecticut Conservation Reporter, "Connecticut Coastal Wetlands Crises." December 1968.
    - Wetlands, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 60-61)
      Evaluation of Inland Wetland and Water Course Functions, The Connecticut Inland Wetlands Project by David Lavine, Charles Dauchy, Dorothy McCluskey, Liz Petry, and Sarah W. Richards.
    - The Candleview Ridge Incorporated, A Scenic Development, 1948 (Folder OS Folder 2, Item 8)
      Map showing subdivisions of development area
  - Streets, Buildings, Structures-Danbury and Regional Towns
    Materials in these file are photocopies of newspaper articles that give the history and description of various streets, buildings and structures in Danbury as the well as regional towns. Researchers should also search the Danbury Preservation Trust Records, which contain in-depth descriptions of sites of architectural and historical significance. Also see Truman Warner Papers Historic Preservation and Post Card Collection. See also: Danbury Preservation Trust Records
    Photograph Collection
    Truman Warner Papers, Historic Preservation
    Truman Warner Papers, Post Card Collection.
    Materials in these file are photocopies of newspaper articles that give the history and description of various streets, buildings and structures in Danbury as the well as regional towns. Researchers should also search the Danbury Preservation Trust Records, which contain in-depth descriptions of sites of architectural and historical significance. Also see Truman Warner Papers Historic Preservation and Post Card Collection. See also: Danbury Preservation Trust Records, Photograph Collection